http://www.cheatcc.com/privacy.html

Cheat Code Central: Privacy Policy
Cheat Code Central respects your privacy and use of the web.
Usage information may be analyzed in order to evaluate our system's performance. Your computer reaches us via a particular IP (Internet Protocol) address. This can reveal the identity of your Internet Service Provider, and their local point-of-presence. This data is compiled into statistics to show the server load and reveal peak usage. None of this information is sold or disseminated to outside parties.
The individual web pages from Cheat Code Central that are requested by your browser are recorded in a server log to allow evaluation of our most popular pages, and to reveal the presence of broken links and other request problems. None of this information is sold or disseminated to outside parties.
Your browser has the ability to use "cookies" which, unless you disable their use, store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to various web sites. When you register for a Cheat Code Central e-mail address, cookies are used to store your login status and preferences. They also are used to limit the number and frequency of various ads displayed as you browse the site. Banner, tower, and other ads displayed through our advertising broker may elect to use cookies to prevent the same ad being displayed too many times to the same user, or to identify Cheat Code Central as the site responsible for a "click-through" for an advertiser. However, cookies can not reveal any personal information about you. None of this information is available to Cheat Code Central, and therefore is not sold or disseminated to outside parties.
Cheat Code Central is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy
Cheat Code Central is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC ("AdThrive") for the purposes of placing advertising on the site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.
A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.
Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.
By using Cheat Code Central, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.
For European Economic Area Residents
If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data maintained by AdThrive related to advertising on Cheat Code Central, you can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)
For California Residents
California law gives residents the right to opt out of the "sale" of their personal information to third parties, including for advertising purposes. Under California law, the sharing of your information with a service provider for advertising purposes could be considered a "sale." To opt out of the sharing of your information for advertising information, click the opt out link provided in the footer of this page. You also have the right to request from us the categories of personal information that we have shared and the categories of third parties to whom the information was provided. To make such a request, please contact us at info@adthrive.com. To be clear we do not share your name, contact information, or any other sensitive information with third parties, and the categories of third parties that we share information with for advertising purposes are supply side platforms, programmatic advertising exchanges, and demand side platforms.
SPOTLIGHT
CheatCC's 2020 Holiday Buyer's Guide
Why the Switch is the PERFECT Second Console!
Is the Oculus on a Quest to Make VR a Success?
No Cyberpunk? No Problem!
Can Gamers Really Trust Facebook?
Top Black Friday Deals: Pandemic Edition!
Marvel's Spider-Man: Miles Morales Review
PlayStation 5 Review
CoD: Black Ops: Cold War Review
Xbox Series X Review
THE WEEKLY POLLDo you think you've gotten Covid-19 yet?Yes, I've tested positive for it.I think so. I didn't get tested, but I feel like I had it.No, I don't think so.I don't know.View Poll History
X
"Like" CheatCC on Facebook
Follow @cheatcc
Home
PS4
Xbox One
PC
Switch
Contact Us
Top StoriesFortnite Returns to iOS, Dragon Age Director's New StudioNew Map/Ships Coming to Squadrons, Crazy Spider-Man GlitchMicrosoft's Bethesda Plans, Snyder Preferred 2-Part Justice LeagueTwitch Apologizes for DMCA, Mortal Kombat Film DelayedSpider-Man Saves Will Transfer on PS5, Remote Play on PS4Sega Sells Arcade Business, Celebrity Coming to Assassin’s CreedMore News...
Don't Miss
Let's Face It...Super Mario is Perfect!
Why We Need to Rethink the Next-Gen
What is the Future of VR Gaming?
Can Microsoft Really Save Gamestop?
Is It Worth Treading Old Ground?
Copyright © 1997-2020 Cheat Code Central. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
